{
    "subject": "resource/Kroonstad",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/South_Africa",
    "human_readable": "Kroonstad is located in South Africa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9038722515106201,
            "question": "Where is Kroonstad located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7611337304115295,
            "question": "What country is Kroonstad in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.600498378276825,
            "question": "What kind of geography does Kroonstad have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5801499485969543,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Kroonstad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5668957233428955,
            "question": "Is Kroonstad a town or a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4464060366153717,
            "question": "What is the population of Kroonstad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4432104527950287,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Kroonstad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3365423083305359,
            "question": "What language(s) are spoken in Kroonstad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22180499136447906,
            "question": "What continent is South Africa on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18655653297901154,
            "question": "Can you name a city in South Africa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kroonstad is located in South Africa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8517_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What continent is South Africa on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8517_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language(s) are spoken in Kroonstad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8517_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Kroonstad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8517_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8517_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple sources of information that confirm Kroonstad's location as being in Free State, South Africa. This information can be found in the following files:\n\n* /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8517/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt\n* /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8517/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt\n* /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8517/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt\n* /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8517/re-ranker-msmarco/67.txt\n* /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8517/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt\n* /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8517/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt\n\nThese files consistently mention that Kroonstad is a city or town in the Free State province of South Africa."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Kroonstad is a city in Free State, which is part of South Africa. Therefore, the statement \"Kroonstad is located in South Africa\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}